I'm Jayna, I'm 35 and I joined Blueprint because I was training at another gym in the
area and was getting much better in terms of my cardio fitness if I wasn't getting stronger
in the ways that I wanted to.
I joined Blueprint about six months ago, so back in April, and since then I've got so
much stronger and feel much more confident and have less pain in my body.
I also have a much better sense of nutrition and how much my nutrition impacts my training
and my ability to get stronger.
Blueprint is honestly my happy place.
I always enjoy coming here, everybody, all the instructors are so friendly and knowledgeable
and somehow know everything about where I was last week and where I want to get to.
In terms of three words that I would use to describe Blueprint, supportive, challenging
and fun.